Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VI: Announcements, 12474
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements, 12475
    - Heffernan, Julie, undated; 12548 (Box 23, Folder 185)
    - Holland Tunnel, undated; 12547 (Box 23, Folder 186)
    - Jacob K. Javits Center, undated; 12546 (Box 23, Folder 187)
    - Jane Street Theatre, undated; 12545 (Box 23, Folder 188)
    - Jan van der Donk, undated; 12544 (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - Jewish Museum, undated; 12543 (Box 23, Folder 190)
    - Joe's Pub, undated; 12542 (Box 23, Folder 191)
    - Key Club, undated; 12541 (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - The Kitchen, undated; 12540 (Box 23, Folder 193)
    - Kitsch Inn, undated; 12539 (Box 23, Folder 194)
    - Knitting Factory, undated; 12538 (Box 23, Folder 195)
    - La Mama, undated; 12537 (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Lark Theatre Company, undated; 12536 (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - Le Bar Bat, undated; 12535 (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - Life, undated; 12534 (Box 23, Folder 199)
    - Life Cafe, undated; 12533 (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - Lightworks, undated; 12532 (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - Little Theater, undated; 12531 (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - Lower East Side Festival, undated; 12530 (Box 23, Folder 203)
    - Luna Lounge, undated; 12529 (Box 23, Folder 204)
    - Marcel Sitcoske Gallery, undated; 12528 (Box 23, Folder 205)
    - Margaret Bodell Gallery, undated; 12527 (Box 23, Folder 206)
    - MASS MoCA, undated; 12526 (Box 23, Folder 207)
    - McIntosh/Panich Gallery, undated; 12525 (Box 23, Folder 208)
    - Medicine Show, undated; 12524 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Studio, undated; 12523 (Box 23, Folder 210)
    - Metronome, undated; 12522 (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - Meulener, Brian, undated; 12521 (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - Millenium Film Workshop, undated; 12520 (Box 23, Folder 213)
    - Mother, undated; 12519 (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - MWF Video Club, undated; 12518 (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - New Museum, undated; 12517 (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - New World Grill, undated; 12516 (Box 23, Folder 217)
    - Ohm, undated; 12515 (Box 23, Folder 218)
    - One Year Performance, undated; 12514 (Box 23, Folder 219)
    - Pangaea, undated; 12513 (Box 23, Folder 220)
    - PaintingsDirect.com, undated; 12512 (Box 23, Folder 221)
    - Pioneer Theater, undated; 12511 (Box 23, Folder 222)
    - Philip Alan Gallery, undated; 12510 (Box 23, Folder 223)
    - POPaganda, undated; 12509 (Box 23, Folder 224)
    - P.P.O.W., undated; 12508 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - Present Co. Theatorium, undated; 12507 (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - Printed Matter, Inc., undated; 12506 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - Public Theater, undated; 12505 (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - REPOhistory, undated; 12504 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - Roger Smith Gallery, undated; 12503 (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - Roxy, undated; 12502 (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - Sakura Park, undated; 12501 (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - Sam Cintron Gallery, undated; 12500 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Sandra Gering Gallery, undated; 12499 (Box 23, Folder 234)
    - Sideshow, undated; 12498 (Box 23, Folder 235)
    - Simon Gallery, undated; 12497 (Box 23, Folder 236)
    - Small Press Book Fair, undated; 12496 (Box 23, Folder 237)
    - Spa, undated; 12495 (Box 23, Folder 238)
    - Spectra Digital Arts Gallery, undated; 12494 (Box 23, Folder 239)
    - Studio 18 Gallery, undated; 12493 (Box 23, Folder 240)
    - Subculture, undated; 12492 (Box 23, Folder 241)
    - System, undated; 12491 (Box 23, Folder 242)
    - Thread Waxing Space, undated; 12490 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Track 16 Gallery, undated; 12489 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Total Theater Lab, undated; 12488 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Tricia Collins Contemporary Art, undated; 12487 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Twirl, undated; 12486 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Upstate Art, undated; 12485 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - USA, undated; 12484 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - VIA Festival, undated; 12483 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Weston, Frederick and Bruce Benderson, undated; 12482 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wetlands Preserve, undated; 12481 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - WFMU Marathon, undated; 12480 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Whitney Museum, undated; 12479 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Yaddo, undated; 12478 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Yankee Clipper, undated; 12477 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Zinsser, John, undated; 12476 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VII: Sound recordings, 12466
  also includes videorecordings
  - Algebra Suicide. The Secret Like Crazy. 1987-Compact Disk., 12473 (Box 30)
  - Algebra Suicide. Swoon. 1991-Compact Disk., 12472 (Box 30)
  - Algebra Suicide. Tongue Wrestling. 1994-Compact Disk., 12471 (Box 30)
  - Huberman, David, Catherine Sand, Susan Scutti at Parkside reading, 12/7/1998. Videotape., 12470 (Box 30)
  - Packer, Eve and Noah Howard. That Look. 2000-Compact Disk., 12469 (Box 30)
  - People's Poetry Gathering, 2001-Compact Disk., 12468 (Box 30)
  - Tomkiw, Lydia. Incorporated, 1995-Compact Disk., 12467 (Box 30)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VIII: Original Art, 12460
  - Digital Art for Digitas, undated; 12465 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Restino, Janet, undated; 12464 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Shalom, undated; 12463 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Misc. drawings, undated; 12462 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified, undated; 12461 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series IX: Ephemera, 12457
  Box 2 of Series IX - Ephemera
  - Two t-shirts designed by Junichi Tsunoda, with poetry by Sharon Mesmer, undated; 12459 (Box 31)
  - One t-shirt entitled Broadshirt with poetry from Japanese avant-garde poets, undated; 12458 (Box 31)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series XII: Catalogs, 12430
  - Anthology Film Archives, Jan.-Mar. 2001, 12450 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Anthology Film Archives, Apr.-Jun. 2001, 12449 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Anthology Film Archives, July-Sept. 2001, 12448 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Burning Deck Books, 2001, 12447 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - four walls eight windows, Fall 2000, 12446 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - four walls eight windows, Spring 2001, 12445 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Hanging Loose Press, 2000-01, 2000-2001; 12444 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Hanging Loose Press, 2001-02, 2001-2002; 12443 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Luzerner Comix-Festival, Mar. 30-Apr, 8, 2001, 12442 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Ram Publications and Distribution, 2000-01, 2000-2001; 12441 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Seven Stories Press, Spring/Summer 2000, 12440 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Seven Stories Press, Fall/Winter 2000, 12439 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Seven Stories Press, Spring-Summer 2001, 12438 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Small Press Distribution, Spring/Summer 2000, 12437 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Small Press Distribution, Fall/Winter 2000-01, 2000-2001; 12436 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Small Press Distribution, Spring/Summer 2001, 12435 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Thin Air Video, undated; 12434 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - U Turn, vol. 1, issue 2, Dec. 2000, 12433 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Verso, Spring 2000, 12432 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Verso, Autumn 2000, 12431 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Oversize - Series XIII: Calendars, 12428
  Added to Oversize box 1 of Series 13
  - 1999 and 2000., 1999, 2000; 12429 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series XIV: Periodicals, 12404
  - American Book Review: Vol. 21, no. 3, Mar.-Apr, 2000: Vol. 21, no. 4, May-Jun. 2000: Vol. 21, no. 5, Jul.-Aug. 2000, 12427 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - American Book Review: Vol. 22, no. 2, Jan-Feb. 2001: Vol. 22, no. 3, Mar.-Apr. 2001: Vol. 22, no. 4, May-Jun. 2001: Vol. 22, no. 5, Jul.-Aug. 2001, 12426 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - The Bridges In Our Lives: Writings by the Students of ASHS Castle Hill, undated; 12425 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Chess Life, May 2000, 12424 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Daily News Magazine, Apr. 22, 1990, 12423 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - The Eclectic, Vol. 2, no. 10, Mar. 2001, 12422 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Goldsmith, Kenneth. Index to the First Edition of Soliloquy., undated; 12421 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Hot, undated; 12420 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Juxtapoz, Vol. 5, no. 1, Spring 1998, 12419 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Lytle, Ellen Aug. from person to page July, 1998, 12418 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Medicinal Purposes, Vol. II, no. IV, Midyear, 2001, 12417 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - New Music Connoisseur, Vol. 9, no, 1, Spring, 2001, 12416 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Phi Kappa Phi Journal, Vol. 81, no. 1, Winter, 2001, 12415 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Poetry Project Newsletter, issue 185, Summer 2001, 12414 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Rain Taxi, Vol. 6, no. 2, Summer, 2001, 12413 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Raven Chronicles, Vol. 10, no.1, undated; 12412 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Simon, John F. Art Report 2001., 12411 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Spinning Jenny, no. 5, 2001, 12410 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Spread the Poet, issue 6, Apr. 2001, 12409 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Underground Surrealist Magazine, issue 11, 1999, 12408 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Washington Free Press, no. 42, Nov.-Dec. 1999, 12407 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Williamsburg Observer, July 4, 2001, 12406 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Zwirn, issue 5, Summer 2000, 12405 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series I: Correspondence, 12367
  - Anthony, Bill, undated; 12403 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Baldi, Malaga, undated; 12402 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Basinski, Michael, undated; 12401 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Curcio, Robert, undated; 12400 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Heather, undated; 12399 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Deyab, Larry, undated; 12398 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Eidus, Janice, undated; 12397 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Englendar, Stephen, undated; 12396 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fagin, Betsy, undated; 12395 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Finberg, Bonny, undated; 12394 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Hansen, Judith, undated; 12393 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Hata, Takashi, undated; 12392 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Hawa, Laura, undated; 12391 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Holder, Douglas, undated; 12390 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated; 12389 (Box 25, Folder 14A)
  - MacPhee, Michael, undated; 12388 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Maurer, Susan, undated; 12387 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Morse, Elizabeth, undated; 12386 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Nodstrand, Judie, undated; 12385 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated; 12384 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Peabody, Richard, undated; 12383 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 12382 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Ratner, Rochelle, undated; 12381 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Rosset, Barney, undated; 12380 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Seweryn, Natalie, undated; 12379 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Sirowitz, Hal, undated; 12378 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Solomon, Tanya, undated; 12377 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Theriopoulos, Georgette, undated; 12376 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Vallone, Peter F. Jr., undated; 12375 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated; 12374 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - White, C., undated; 12373 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Wilson, Peter Lamborn, undated; 12372 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Witz, Bob, undated; 12371 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Wright, Jeff, undated; 12370 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Postits from multiple correspondents, undated; 12369 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified/Partial Name, undated; 12368 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series II: Manuscripts, 12324
  - Basinski, Michael--Book Reviews, undated; 12366 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Blagg, Max--Hospital Food, undated; 12365 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Chomsky, Noam--9-11, undated; 12364 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Cory, Jean-Jacques--Academic Critics of the Avant-Garde, undated; 12363 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Dalachinsky, Steve--"A Free Lancing of Freelance", undated; 12362 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Dombrowski, Bob--The War Years, undated; 12361 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Afterword: Any Good Books…, undated; 12360 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Feast, Jim "AIDS: A Second Opinion", undated; 12359 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Pitch), undated; 12358 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Prelude), undated; 12357 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 1/4), undated; 12356 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 2/4), undated; 12355 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 3/4), undated; 12354 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--Freelance (Working MS 4/4), undated; 12353 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Freelance 1/2, undated; 12352 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Freelance 2/2, undated; 12351 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Return to Sender: The Ed Zines Story (working MS), undated; 12350 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)-- Return to Sender: The Ed Zines Story, undated; 12349 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Feast, Jim--"Review of Steve Dalachinsky's A Superintendent's Eyes", undated; 12348 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Feast, Jim (with Ron Kolm)--"Unbearable Portfolio Three, Theme Collaboration", undated; 12347 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Feast, Jim --Untitled MS, undated; 12346 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Feast, Jim --Draft of Untitled Novel, undated; 12345 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Huberman, David--Full Circle, undated; 12344 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Kolm, Ron--Westbeth Application, undated; 12343 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard--Essays, undated; 12342 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Kupferburg, Tuli--Uranus, undated; 12341 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Life, Kathy, undated; 12340 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Nostrand, Judie--Poems, undated; 12339 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Public Illumination Magazine [materials], undated; 12338 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Nufer, Doug--Atlas Slugged, undated; 12337 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated; 12336 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Pritchard, A. A., undated; 12335 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Rosset, Barney--Our Humanity is Still Here, undated; 12334 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus--Sex-Fiend Monologues (MS and Proof), undated; 12333 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus--White and Wong, undated; 12332 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Savage, Tom, undated; 12331 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Sparrow--Poem, undated; 12330 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Sykes, Floyd--I'm Your Man 1/2, undated; 12329 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sykes, Floyd--I'm Your Man 2/2, undated; 12328 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tsongas, George [poems], undated; 12327 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Witz, Bob--"A Proposal", undated; 12326 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Zummer, Thomas--Some Notes on the Unspeakable, undated; 12325 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series III: The Unbearables, 12272
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables, 12293
    - Help Yourself Reading, 5/23/1997; 12323 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Unbearables Portfolio #3, 2001; 12322 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Assembling Magazine #13 [materials], undated; 12321 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Assembling Magazine #13, 9/2001; 12320 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Assembling Magazine #14 [materials], undated; 12319 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Assembling Magazine #14, 10/28/2001; 12318 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Beatfest 2002 Flyer and Program, 4/12/2002; 12317 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Assembling Magazine #15 [materials], undated; 12316 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Assembling Magazine #15, 4/28/2002; 12315 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Colored White Women Artists [materials], undated; 12314 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Colored White Women Artists Catalogue, 5/04/2002; 12313 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Colored White Women Artists Flyers, 5/04/2002; 12312 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival Program [materials], undated; 12311 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival Program, 5/2002; 12310 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival Clippings, 5/2002; 12309 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Unbearables Arts Festival, undated; 12308 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Malcolm McLaren: Not for Sale, 8/27/2002; 12307 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - National Post Article, 8/30/2002; 12306 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - New York Sun Article, 2002; 12305 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Assembling Magazine #16 [materials], undated; 12304 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Assembling Magazine #16, 10/13/2002; 12303 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Help Yourself Readings, multiple dates; 12302 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Smithsonian Article, 11/2002; 12301 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Help Yourself Reading, 3/27/2003; 12300 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Call for entries: Life Café book, undated; 12299 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Drink Policy, undated; 12298 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Help Yourself Reading, undated; 12297 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Life-Time Non-Achievement Award Tuli Kupfenberg, undated; 12296 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - World's Longest Love Poem, undated; 12295 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Worst Book Reading, undated; 12294 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Subseries C: Help Yourself, 12273
    - Related Correspondence, undated; 12292 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Research Materials, undated; 12291 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Used and Unused Manuscripts (1/3), undated; 12290 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Used and Unused Manuscripts (2/3), undated; 12289 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Used and Unused Manuscripts (3/3), undated; 12288 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - 3 ¼ inch floppy discs IBM format, undated; 12287 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - 3 ¼ inch floppy discs IBM and Mac formats, undated; 12286 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Used and Unused Graphics, undated; 12285 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Jim Feast forward and afterward MS, undated; 12284 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Box Top/Checklist for First Typescript, undated; 12283 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - First Typescript (1/2), undated; 12282 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - First Typescript (2/2), undated; 12281 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Second Typescript, undated; 12280 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Cover Graphic, proof, undated; 12279 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - First Proof, undated; 12278 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Corrected Proof (incomplete), undated; 12277 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Second Proof (1/2), undated; 12276 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Second Proof (2/2), undated; 12275 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Final Proof, undated; 12274 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series IV: Subject Files, 12190
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists, 12224
    - Appearances Magazine, undated; 12271 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Anthony, William, undated; 12270 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Aronson, David, undated; 12269 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Azon, Gary, undated; 12268 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Blagg, Max, undated; 12267 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Chicks on Speed, undated; 12266 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Collins, Billy (shelved in oversize box), undated; 12265 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Cronenberg, David, undated; 12264 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cusimano, Mick, undated; 12263 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Daitch, Susan, undated; 12262 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Dalachinsky, Steven, undated; 12261 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Dombrowski, Bob, undated; 12260 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Doucet, Julie, undated; 12259 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Feast, Jim, undated; 12258 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - FLY, undated; 12257 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Gray, Spaulding, undated; 12256 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Hughes Brothers, undated; 12255 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Hunter, Keshav, undated; 12254 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated; 12253 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Kaz, undated; 12252 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated; 12251 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Krigstein, Bernard, undated; 12250 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Lane, Tim, undated; 12249 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Long, Donald, undated; 12248 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Maurer, Susan (shelved in oversize box), undated; 12247 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Mesmer, Susan, undated; 12246 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - No-Neck Blues Band, undated; 12245 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Nufer, Doug, undated; 12244 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Otomo, Yuko, undated; 12243 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Pincus, Henry, undated; 12242 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Pyle, Kevin, undated; 12241 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Rutkowski, Thad, undated; 12240 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Rutkowski, Thad (as Hip Hop Sing), undated; 12239 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Seth, undated; 12238 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Seth (shelved in oversize box), undated; 12237 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated; 12236 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Sonnenfeld, Mark, undated; 12235 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Sparrow, undated; 12234 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Sparrow (shelved in oversize box), undated; 12233 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Spiegelman, Arthur, undated; 12232 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Topp, Mike, undated; 12231 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Ulin, David, undated; 12229 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Welch, Sean Michael, undated; 12228 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated; 12227 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Witz, Bob, undated; 12226 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Zummer, Tom, undated; 12225 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects, 12191
    - Bitaemo (Ukranian Restaurant), undated; 12223 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Coliseum Books, Ron Kolm collage, undated; 12222 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Coliseum Books, Boycott Flyer, undated; 12221 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Coliseum Books, Patron Business Cards, undated; 12220 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Coliseum Books, store closing, memos, undated; 12219 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Coliseum Books, store closing, Ron Kolm interview, undated; 12218 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Coliseum Books, store closing, clippings, undated; 12217 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Coliseum Books, correspondence, Anthony Ballard, undated; 12216 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Coliseum Books, correspondence, Ron Kolm, undated; 12215 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Coliseum Books, correspondence, John Underwood, undated; 12214 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Coliseum Books, misc. correspondence, undated; 12213 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Coliseum Books, employee art, Meg's Hats, undated; 12212 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Coliseum Books, employee art, cards by Patrick Stevenson, undated; 12211 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Coliseum Books, misc. employee art, undated; 12210 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Coliseum Books, ephemera, undated; 12209 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Coliseum Books, flyers, undated; 12208 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Coliseum Books, invitations, undated; 12207 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Coliseum Books, ID cards, Ron Kolm, undated; 12206 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Coliseum Books, Only in New York, undated; 12205 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Coliseum Books, policies, information, undated; 12204 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Coliseum Books, press clippings, undated; 12203 (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - Coliseum Books, re-opening, undated; 12202 (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Coliseum Books, sound recording, employee mix CD-RS, undated; 12201 (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Coliseum Books, sound recording, None of the Above "Feel Like a Dog" 45 inch single, 1983; 12200 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Coliseum Books, staff events, undated; 12199 (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Coliseum Books, in-store readings, undated; 12198 (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Klezmer, undated; 12197 (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Pacifica Radio, undated; 12196 (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Semiotext(e), undated; 12195 (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - September 11th 2001, undated; 12194 (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - Shakespeare and Company, undated; 12193 (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Soft Skull Press, undated; 12192 (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series V: Photographs, 12184
  - Subseries A: Photographs, 12187
    - 2 photos of Ron Kolm at the Nuyorican, undated; 12189 (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - 2 photos of Ron Kolm reading at Bergen Community College, undated; 12188 (Box 27, Folder 80)
- Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VI: Announcements, 12049
  - Subseries A: Readings, 12120
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 12183 (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Anthology Film Archives, undated; 12182 (Box 27, Folder 82)